var quiz = [
    {question: '126 + 79', solution: 205},
    {question: '12 x 6 - 13', solution: 59},
    {question: '122 : 4', solution: 30.5},
    {question: '5Â³ - 12', solution: 113},
    {question: '99 x 9', solution: 891},
    {question: '7.3 x 4', solution: 29.2},
    {question: '35 - 29 x 2', solution: -23},
    {question: '30 Prozent von 80', solution: 24},
    {question: '110 : 11 : 5', solution: 2},
    {question: '16 x 17', solution: 272},
    {question: '109 + 44 + 17 + 81', solution: 251},
    {question: '-9.3 + 12.4', solution: 3.1},
    {question: '181 x 3 - 15 x 4', solution: 483},
    {question: '0.2 x 30', solution: 6},
    {question: '55 : 0.5', solution: 110}
];